（古市）《オレたちの長い長～い
夏休みは終わった。→
Our long, long summer vacation is over!
そして！そして！！そしてぇ～！！》
And... And...
And!!!
男鹿～！起きてるよな～！
Oga, you're awake, right?!
（男鹿）ぐ～っ　ぐ～っ…。
（ベル坊）ぐ～っ　ぐ～っ…。
（古市）起きて…ない？
You're not... awake.
ファ～。
ダ～。
何だよ　こんな朝っぱらから。
What's with you, so bright and early?
（古市）何って　今日から
新学期だろ～が！！
What's with me?! Today's
the start of the new term!
ハァ？新学期？
学校ぶっ壊れたまんまだろ？
New term? But the school's still busted up.
お前なぁ～！コレ
読んでないのかよ～！ホレ！
Why, you... Didn't you even read it?
あ？
ダ～ブ？
Here!
転校のごあんない？
"Notice of transfer"?
Attention all Students
Notice of Transfer
Please go to here, okay?
The New Term Has Started
（カンカン…）
しっかし　めんどくせ～なぁ。
But man, what a pain...
なんでわざわざ　別の高校に
通わなきゃ　なんね～んだよ。
ダブ　アイアイ。
Why do we have to go all the
way to a different school?
だからっ！！
お前が壊したからだろ　お前が！
Because you destroyed ours! Yeah, you!
（校長）うっ　ううう…。
あ～そんな事もあったような…。
アイ！
Oh... I kinda remember something like that.
（古市）まあ　転校つっても
校舎が直るまでの間→
Well, it's just temporary until they
repair the school building though.
間借りするだけなんだけどな。
けど　ウチの生徒メチャメチャ
多いんだろ？どうすんだ？
But don't we have, like, a ton of students?
How's this work?
だから　いくつかの高校に
分散させるんだってよ。
That's why they've split us up into
groups that go to different schools.
へ～。
ダー。
ではここで　オレたちの行く
学校を紹介しましょう！
Now allow me to introduce the
school which we will be going to!
St. Ishiyama Academy
（梓）＜聖石矢魔学園は　地区内でも
有数の進学校で→
St. Ishiyama Academy has the highest
college acceptance rates in the area.
生徒たちの自主性を重んじる→
The students there are allowed
a great deal of independence,
自由な校風でも
知られる学園です。→
and the academy is known for
its free and open atmosphere!
生徒は男子と女子がほぼ半々で→
The student population is about
evenly split between boys and girls,
校内には　カフェテリアなどの
レクリエーション施設も充実。→
and there is a cafeteria and
recreation facilities on campus!
クラブ活動も盛んで　みな思い思い
の青春を謳歌しています＞
With an abundance of club activities,
everyone celebrates their
never-to-be-forgotten youth!
The End.
と　ゆ～ことで！
And there you have it.
St. Ishiyama Academy
やってきました～！
聖石矢魔学園！！
We're here at St. Ishiyama Academy!
くぅ～っ！キタキター！！
We're here! We're here!
あ～？なあ　お前　朝から妙にテンション高くねえか？
Aren't you a little too hyped up
for this early in the morning?
これが　テンション
上げずにいられるかっ！！
And how could I not be hyped up?!
（古市）《あの不良共の巣窟から
ときはなたれ→
Flown free from those foul delinquents,
オレたちにも　ついに
ごくごく普通の→
when I think of how we'll finally experience
the oh-so-normal and sweet days of youth...
さわやかな青春の日々が
訪れるかと思うと～》
くうぅ～！
ん～。
んお？男鹿　アレ見ろ！
あん？
Oga, check that out!
あはは…。
うふふ…。
へえ～。
はぁ～。アハ　アハハ…。
オレ　生きててよかった～ううっ。
はぁ～。
I'm so glad I'm alive!
（古市）うっうっ…。
どうしたの？
何かアレって変質者みたい。
What's wrong?
Um, I think that's a pervert...
ウッソでしょ～！
（女子達）や～だ　ちょっと…エッ！！
You've gotta be kidding me!
Ew, stay away...
あ？フフフ…転校初日だけに→
I just transferred here, so I'd
better make a good impression.
ここは好印象を
与えておかないとな。
やぁ～！キミたち→
Hi! Are you students here at St. Ishiyama...
聖石矢魔学園の…。
（女子達）いやぁ～！
いや　その…え？
Uh...
オイ　それより
早く教室に行こうぜ。
ダーブ！
Hey, hurry up and go to the classroom.
え？あ　そうだな。
Oh, right.
今日からオレたちの
新しい学園生活が始まるんだ。
Today marks the start
of our new school lives.
新しいクラスメートとも
早く打ち解けておかないとな！
We had better break the ice with
our new classmates without delay...
フッハッハッハ！
（古市の鼻歌）
Ishiyama High - Special Class
（古市）おっ！ここか。
だな。
アイ。
Here?
Looks like it.
（古市の咳払い）
おっはよ～ござ…い…。
Good mor~nin...
（古市）えっ…え～と　うっ！！
U-Um...
って　これは…？
W-What is this?
あぁん？
ダ？
（ヒルダ）妙だな。
（アランドロン）と言いますと？
This is odd.
And by that you mean...?
うむ。学校というもの仕組みは
よくわからんのだが→
Hm. I do not know much about these
institutions known as schools,
通常は学年というもので
クラスを分けるのだろう？
but they usually separate the
classes based on year, yes?
おっしゃる通りです。
Exactly as you say.
確か　東条は３年
邦枝は２年だったはず。
If I recall, Tojo is a third year,
and Kunieda should be a second year.
ならば　１年の男鹿と同じクラスに
いるのは　おかしいのではないか？
Then, is it not strange that they are
in the same class as Oga, a first year?
はっ！たしかに…。
（アクババ）クケーッ！！
Indeed!
（神崎）オイ　こりゃ
ど～なんてんだ？１年坊。
Hey... What's the meaning of this, frosh?
いや～そんなこと
オレに言われても…。
Uh, don't ask me!
あぁ！？こっち向けやコラァ！！
Huh? Look at me, damn it!
何が悲しくて　こんな連中と同じ
教室にいなきゃなんね～んだよ！！
Why do I have to get stuck
in a class with all of you?
（寧々）それはこっちのセリフよ！
（千秋）うんうん。
That's my line.
あん？
（姫川）まぁまぁ。
い～んじゃないの　別に。
Now, now... Is it really such a problem?
オレは悪くないと思うぜ
このクラス。特に席順がいい。
I don't think this class is so bad at all.
I especially like the seating
assignment. Don't you, Aoi-chan?
ね　葵ちゃん。
（邦枝）べ　別にいいとか
悪いとかじゃないし。
It's not something that's "good" or "bad"...
先生が決めたことなんだから
仕方ないっていうか　その…。
The teacher decided it, so there's
nothing we can do about it... It's...
ファ～。
（由加）
《それにしても…東邦神姫→
But wait... The TKKH...
グッドナイト下川
キラーマシン阿部→
Good Night Shimokawa...
Abe the Killing Machine...
ＭＫ５の各先輩方まで
いらっしゃるし→
Even all the members of the MK5 are here!
まじ　コンプリートって感じっス！ムフ～》
This is like, a full set, totally!
（東条）お前ら！
Asswipes!
（どよめき）
（東条）んなことより→
Enough of this...
そろそろバイトの時間なんだが…。
It's about time for my
part-time job, actually...
《さっすが東条先輩！→
That's Tojo-senpai for you!
この状況で全く動じてないっスよ
。
さすがっス！！》
Even in a situation like this, he's
not shaken a bit! Totally awesome!
ケッ。どうせアレだろ？
ウチの学校　バカばっかだし→
You know it's gonna be that...
Our school's full of idiots,
学年まとめても問題ね～とか
思われてんだろ。なっ　ボウズ。
so they don't think it'll be a
problem to stick us all together.
Ain't that right, kid?
ウイ？ダ！アイ！
（姫川）
ま　なんつ～か　こんなカオスも
面白いんじゃないかな？
Well, I suppose this might spark
some interesting chaos...
そう思うだろ？ボクちゃん？
ダ！アイ！
Don't you think so too, lil' buddy?
《あぁ…みんなアレか。→
Oh... Everyone's doing that.
いまいち　どう会話していいか
わかんないから→
They don't know how to talk to
each other without making waves,
とりあえず　当たりさわりのない
ベル坊に話しかけてんのか…》
so they talk to harmless-looking
Baby Beel...
ダ！アイ！
ふわぁ～。
朝っぱらから叩き起こされたんで
眠くてよ～。
ニョ？
I'm sleepy from getting woken
up early this morning...
あ？あっ！！
《やだ…こいつ
こんな無邪気な寝顔するんだ》
Oh, my! Look at him... He sleeps
with such a innocent face...
《ま～た　始まったよ》
There she goes again...
（コツコツ…）
（ドアが開く音）
（佐渡原）
お前ら　おとなしく席についてろ。
You brats, take your seats and stay quiet.
今日から　このクラスの
担任になった…佐渡原だ。
I'm going to be the homeroom
teacher for this class...
Sadohara Takumi
Sadohara.
フッ。聞けば　お前らは
あのゴミ高校の中でも→
I heard you folks are the top-class
trash at your dump of a high school.
トップクラスのゴミらしいが
この聖石矢魔に来たからには→
If you think you can carry on here at St.
Ishiyama the way you did before, you're...
今までのような
生活が送れるとは…思うなよ。
...seriously mistaken.
ん？ファ～。
《なんだコイツ…》
What's with this guy?
ま　今日のところは…ん？
Well then, today, we're going...
《フム。アイツにするか。
クククッ…所詮はこいつら→
Let's use him.
In the end these guys are just
a bunch of worthless brutes!
腕力にものを言わせてる
クズの集まり。→
クラスで１番強そうなヤツを
最初に叩きのめせば…》
If I whack down the strongest
one right from the start...
（佐渡原）オイ　そこのお前！
あ？
Hey, you there.
ちょっとした親睦の意味で　軽く
腕ずもうでもやってみるか？ん？
Why don't we have a friendly arm wrestling
match as a way of getting to know each other?
はぁ…でも勝てるかな？
Do you think you can win?
《ヘッヘヘヘ…残念だったな。
こう見えてもオレは学生時代→
Too bad for you...
I might not look it, but when I was in
school I was undefeated in the arm wrestling club!
アームレスリング部で
無敗を誇った男》
((うおりゃあ～！！))
（佐渡原）
《人呼んで
ゴールデンアーム佐渡原》
People called me Golden Arm Sadohara!
（佐渡原）それじゃ　レディー→
Now then... Ready...
ゴ…。
Go!
あ　やべ　やりすぎた…。
Crap, overdid it.
あっ　あっ…。
ハッハハ…ハハハ…
キミ～なかなかやるじゃないか。
You... You have some skill there!
いや～まいったな～。
今日は　いまいち調子が悪かった。
Well, my bad then... I guess I
wasn't feeling so well today...
《このオレの
ゴールデンアームが～！？→
M-My Golden Arm!
痛いっ！すごく痛いっ！！だが
ここで弱味を見せたら…ん？》
It hurts! It really, seriously hurts!
But if I show weakness here...
（男鹿・ベル坊）くか～くか～。
《おお！いいカモ発見！→
I found me a pushover!
取り合えず　弱っちそうな
コイツを見せしめに…》
For now, I'll make an example
out of this weakling...
（佐渡原）オイ　そこのお前！
んあ？
Hey, you over there.
お前　授業中に
なに居眠りしてんだ？あぁん？
What the heck do you think you're
doing sleeping during class?
（古市）あの　先生そいつは…。
お前は黙ってろ！！
Um, Sensei, he's...
You, be quiet!
（佐渡原）聞こえないのか！
ん？あ？
You didn't hear me?
（佐渡原）
何だ　その赤ん坊は！？
ここは保育所じゃないんだぞ！！
What the hell is that baby?
This ain't nursery school!
ハア…。
ハアじゃないっ！→
Yeah...
Don't give me "yeah"! Why don't you
come with me to the teacher's office?
ちょっと職員室に来てもらおうか。
ウ　ウイー。
ヨッ…。
ウッ…。
（一同）うわ～！！
（佐渡原）オラッ！早く起きろ！！
Now, hurry and wake up!
ビィイ～…。
ん？
ダーダダ…。
ダ～！！
（男鹿・佐渡原）ギャア～！！
My name is Yamamura Kazuya.
（山村）《オレの名前は山村和也。→
Right now, I am violently nervous!
今　オレはモーレツに
緊張している。そう…→
That's right...
Because finally, I can
meet the ones I idolize!
憧れていた存在に　ようやく
会うことができるからだ》
（山村）ハァハァ…→
Ishiyama High Special Class
お！ここか。ん？
Here?
Warning: Normal Students, Stay Away!
ハァーッ　やっと終わったぁ。
Finally over...
That guy's the pits.
（寧々）も～サイアクのメンツ！
（千秋）うん。
（山村）《あれは！？》
That's...
《あれは　関東最強のレディース
レッド・テイル！？→
Those are the strongest ladies in
the Kantou region, the Red Tails!
すげぇ　いきなり大物だ！》
Incredible! The big fish, right off the bat!
葵姉さん　何してんスか～？
みんな行っちゃうッスよ～？
What're you doing, Madam Aoi?
Everyone's like, totally leaving!
Even watching from over here, I
can sense their killer spirit!
（山村）《こっから見てるだけで
すさまじい殺気が→
ビンビン伝わってくるぜ！→
Should I get up the courage
and head over there?
ここはひとつ　勇気を出して
行ってみるか？いや　まだだ》
No, not yet.
Huh? Wait a sec...
え～ちょっと待って～。ファ…。
I haven't seen the most crucial person yet!
（山村）《肝心のあの人を
まだ見てないっ！！》
Hurry up and get out here!
早く出てこいっ…。
What's up?
（梓）≪なにが～？≫
んぁ？
（梓）ん？
うおあっ！！アズサ～！？
Azusa!
What, what? What's going to show up?
ナニナニ？何が出てくるの～？
アズサ！お前　なに勝手に
ついてきてんだ！？
は？
Azusa, what are you doing following me?!
ここが　どういう場所か
わかってんのかよ！？
Do you understand what
kind of a place this is?
You shouldn't be here either, Kazu-kun.
（梓）
カズくんこそ　いけないんだよ～。
The teacher at morning assembly told
us it was a bunch of delinquents,
ここは不良のたまり場だから→
絶対　近付いちゃいけないって
朝礼で先生がぁ。
and we should not go near for any reason.
Ah, man! Come with me for a bit!
あ～も～っ！
ちょっと　こっち来い！
（梓）あっ！ちょっと…。
Hey, wait!
（梓）エへヘ　カズくんと手つなぐの
幼稚園の時以来だぁ。
We haven't held hands since
pre-school, Kazu-kun!
Whatever!
（山村）い～から！！
Listen up, Azusa.
（山村）いいか　アズサ。
（梓）はいはい？
Yes-yes?
I'll tell you the truth since
we're childhood friends...
幼なじみのお前だから
正直に言うが…。
はいはい…あっ　え～っと…。
あ？
Yes-yes...
Um...
Isn't it embarrassing saying
"childhood friends" at this point?
あのさ　今どき幼なじみなんて
ハズかしくな～い？
Whatever, enough about that!
だから　そこはイイんだよっ！！
Uh, so, basically...
あ～その　つまり何だ…。
Honestly speaking, I look up to delinquents.
オレはハッキリ言って
不良というものに憧れている。
Oh, I know that.
（梓）うん　知ってるよ！
あ？
Kazu-kun, you suddenly died your
hair and got your ear pieced, right?
カズくん　急に髪の毛そめて
ピアスつけてきたもんね～！
Everyone was talking about
your summer vacation debut!
み～んなウワサしてるよ～
夏休みデビュー。
うっ…あ！オイ！キャッ！
Hey!
You idiot, stop followin' me everywhere.
（神崎）あのな　イチイチ
ついてくんじゃね～よ。
I was thinkin' of observing
the girls' tennis club.
女子テニス部でも
見物しようと思ってな～。
And where might you be headed?
そっちこそ　どちらまで？
ヨーグルッチの自販機見つけたんで→
I found me a vending machine that sells
Yogurty, so I'm going to buy some!
買いに行くんだよ！文句あっか！
Got a problem with that?
No, no...
（姫川）いえいえ…ククク…。
Whoa...
《すげえ…あれはたしか
神崎一と姫川竜也…→
If I'm not mistaken, that's Kanzaki
Hajime and Himekawa Tatsuya!
伝説の東邦神姫のメンバーまで
見られる機会なんて→
Getting to see two members of the legendary
TKKH like this is a real treat!
めったにないぞ！
ハンパない威圧感を感じるぜ…→
I can sense they're some seriously bad dudes.
Is that what they call a killer's aura?!
あれが殺気というヤツか！！》
はっは～
怖そうな人達だったね～。
They're definitely some pretty scary people.
You wanna be like that, Kazu-kun?
カズくんも
あんな風になりたいの？
Don't be silly. The only one
in my sights is Oga-san.
バカ言え　オレの目当ては
あくまで男鹿さんだぜ？
もっとスゲーに決まってんだろ？
男鹿さん？
It's gotta be someone more amazing!
Oga-san?
ヘークシッ！！
だぁ～ヤベエな　こりゃあ…
カゼか？
This ain't good.
A cold?
I thought idiots like
you can't catch colds.
バカのくせに何言ってやがる。
But they say that only
idiots catch summer colds.
ほら　夏カゼはバカしかひかない
っていうだろ。
So you agree about the idiot part?
バカなのはいいのね。
ダーブ！
ん？ああ　そろそろハラへったか？
ダーッ！
Oh, are you getting hungry?
Then let's hurry home.
んじゃ　早めに帰っか。
ダブー！
（山村）むぅ…見ろ
あれが伝説の男鹿さんだ。
Look... That's the legendary Oga-san.
へ～　なんか
あんまり怖くないねぇ。
He doesn't seem that scary at all!
ホントに　あの人なの？
…と　思う。
Is that really him?
...I think.
He looks like a nice daddy!
なんだか
いいパパさんって感じ～。→
And the baby on his back is the cutest!
背中の赤ちゃんも　か～い～ね！
Indeed... Is that really the
legendary Oga Tatsumi-san?
《たしかに…あれが本当に伝説の
男鹿辰巳さんなのか？→
Compared to Kanzaki-san and Himekawa-san,
he's lacking that sort of...
神崎さんや姫川さんに比べて
パッとしないというか…。→
No, that can't be!
いやいや！そんな事はない！
あのウワサは本当のハズ！→
That rumor should be true!
He defeated delinquent after
delinquent that came at him...
おそいかかる不良どもを
次々になぎたおし→
A violent kid who enjoys making
others grovel before him!
土下座させて　よろこぶ暴君…→
Nicknamed "The Rampaging
Ogre" and "The BoB Brawler"!
あだ名はアバレオーガとも
子連れ番長とも呼ばれる男…→
そして　群雄割拠の石矢魔高校を→
And he's the only first-year
to ever rise to the top
たった１人でまとめ上げた
伝説の１年生！》
of the fierce battlefield
that is Ishiyama High!
ガッハハハハ！
Yeah... That's right.
《そうだ…そうだよな…→
If the Baby-on-Board Brawler thing
is right, so should the rest.
子連れ番長っていうくらいだから
まちがいないハズ…→
Should be, anyway...
ハズだけど…》
よしっ　とにかく追うぞ！
よしきた！
Right! Anyway, we'll follow them!
Okay, here we go!
（梓）なんだか　テレビの刑事モノ
みたいで楽しいね！
It's like we're gumshoes on TV! How fun!
Why don't you try being a little nervous?!
（山村）いいから少しは緊張しろ！
（梓）だってぇ～。
But...
（山村・梓）ハァハァハァ…。
ん？
うあ～！
うおっとぉ！
ああっ！あ…あ…。
ん？
（山村）《と　東邦神姫
最強といわれている→
The one said to be the strongest
of the TKKH, Tojo Hidetora!
東条英虎がぁ～！？う…。→
くっ…いかんっ！このままじゃ
アズサまで巻き込んで…》
I can't!
At this rate, Azusa would get involved...
Hey, you there.
なあ　そこの。
（山村）ハイーッ！！
（梓）あ？
Yes?!
この辺にジャプドナルドって
ハンバーガー屋はないか？
Is there a hamburger shop
around here called Japdonalds?
I'm starting a part-time job there today.
今日からバイトに行くんだが。
Oh, it's a little closer to the station.
あ～　それなら
もうちょっと駅の方ですよ。
I see. Thanks for your help.
（東条）そうか。スマン　助かった。
（去って行く足音）
プハーッ！死ぬかと思った～。
I thought I was dead meat!
That guy really seemed strong.
今の人　強そうだったね～。
強いに決まってんだろ！
Well, duh!
That's Tojo Hidetora, the
strongest of the TKKH!
東邦神姫最強の東条英虎だぞ！へえ～。
But you know, Oga-san even beat that...
けどな　あの男鹿さんは
その東条すらも…って！？
へっ？
Crap, I lost sight of him!
（山村）いかん　見失った！
急いで追いかけるぞ！
（梓）がってんだ！
Let's hurry after him!
Agreed!
I was just thinking this... But your
hands have gotten bigger, haven't they?
さっきも思ったんだけどさ
カズくん　手おっきくなったよね。
Who cares about that?
そんなことはいいんだよ！
I've got to figure out
if he's the real Oga-san!
あの人が本物の男鹿さんかどうか
確かめないと！→
どこ行ったんだよ　ったく！
ブー！
Where'd he go, damn it?
ハァハァ…ここか？うっ！？
は？
Here?
Crap!
ヤバ…！
We heard the rumors...
（斜落）ウワサには聞いてるぜ
石矢魔のカスども～。
You're Ishiyama trash!
ハァ。ようやく平和な学園生活が
送れるかと思えば…。
And here I went thinking we'd finally
be able to have peaceful school days...
You're starting to go to that
St. Ishiyama Academy, right?
（斜落）オメーら今日から
あの聖石矢魔学園に→
通うことになったんだってな～。
Sorry, buddy.
ワリィな…。
あ？
He's getting hungry.
コイツがハラすかしてんだ。
通るぞ。
ダ！
Let us through.
ヘヘッ　ビビッて
逃げようとしてんじゃね～ぞ！→
Don't go runnin' away all scared!
Listen up! This here's
the turf of Teimo Tech!
い～か　ここいらはオレたち
帝毛工業のナワバリだ。→
You start somethin' around here,
and you're gonna get hurt!
あんま　でけ～ツラしてっと
痛い目にあわせ…。
Owwy...
（斜落）イタイ…。
斜落さん！
大丈夫ッスか？
Sharaku-san!
You okay?
ん～やっぱカゼか？調子わりぃ。
そ～かあ？
Yeah, it's a cold...
I feel like crap.
You do?
No need to double check! He's the real-deal!
（山村）
《確めるまでもなく本物だ～！》
（梓）《あ…ああ…》
（山村）こんなん　初めて見た。
I've never seen something like that before...
You bastards! How dare you
do that to Sharaku-san!
テメーら　よくも斜落さんを
あんな目に～！！
いや　だから急いでるんだって。
（山村・梓）キャーッ！
But I told you I was in a hurry.
（山村）ちょっ…はなせよ！
≪おとなしくしやがれ！≫
（古市）何だ？
Let us go!
Be good and stay quiet!
What's that?
ヘヘヘへ…これが見えね～か。
（山村・梓）ううっ…。
Can't you see these?
Uh... Don't ring a bell.
あ～…誰？
さ～？
Dunno.
Idiots! These are students from St. Ishiyama!
バーカ！こいつら聖石矢魔の
生徒さんだよぉ！
Great going!
でかした！
オラッ！何か言ってみろ！
Now just try somethin'!
エヘヘ！一般の生徒さん
巻き込んだとなっちゃ→
Get normal students mixed up
in this, and you'll pay for it!
テメーら
タダじゃすまね～よなぁ？
そうなの？
ん～ま　そうかなぁ？
We will?
Sure, I guess?
（山村）
《クッ…やっぱりオレ達が→
I knew it... This isn't a world
where we can set foot in so easily!
簡単に立ち入っていいような
世界じゃなかったんだ…》
Kazu-kun!
（梓）カズくぅ～ん…。
Plus, I ended up getting Azusa involved...
（山村）
《しかも　アズサまで
巻き込んじまうなんて…。→
クッ…このままじゃアズサは
不良達にさらわれて…。→
At this rate, Azusa will be at the
mercy of those delinquents...
Damn it... I gotta stop being a failure as
a man before I even try to be a brawler!
くそっ！不良以前にオレは…
オレは…男としての資格すら！》
ヘヘヘッ！
ど～した　ど～したぁ！
What's wrong, eh?
Let them go!
（邦枝）その子達を放しなさい！
へ！？
Huh?
ぐあっ！
だぁっ！
おぉっ！
（山村）何だ！？
What the...
≪おぉっ！≫
≪うわっ！≫
はっ！？
（不良達）うおぉっ～！！
あんた達こそ…
わかってるんでしょうね。
And you people need to understand, yes?
From now on, we won't just stand by when you
lay hands on students from St. Ishiyama, got it?
今後　聖石矢魔の生徒に
手を出したら→
ウチらが　だまってないよ。
Kunieda Aoi from the TKKH!
（山村）《東邦神姫の…邦枝葵！》
フゥ　やれやれだな。
さてと…。
アイ！
Sheesh...
Now then...
待たせたなぁ～。
Sorry to have kept you waiting...
うひっ！
あの…その…。
Uh... We...
オラオラオラオラオラ～！
Bu-Bu-Burying Punch!
メリメリ！コミコミ！パーンチ！
（不良達）うおおぉ…。
お～　カゼ治ったみてぇだ。
Looks like my cold's better!
ダ～。
ムムム…。
おいっ！ちょっ　待て。
Hey, uh, wait! Hey!
おいっ！
（不良達）ん？
ダ～～ッ！！
（一同）ぎゃあ～！！
（不良達）ああ…。
ダ…。
やっと　おさまったか。
Finally calmed down?
なかなか慣れないもんだな　これ。
This really isn't something
you can get used to...
What was that?
（山村）《今のは何だ！？電撃！？けど
人間がそんな技を？→
Electricity?
But, humans can't do...
No, wait.
いや待てよ…アマゾン川に住む
デンキウナギも→
They say electric eels in the Amazon can
produce as much as an 800 volt shock instantly.
瞬間最大８００ボルトもの
高圧電流を発するという…。→
Maybe if a human trains hard enough...
人間も修行をつめば…でも
どれほどの修行が必要なんだ！》
But, how much training would that take?!
Man, you really saved us, Kunieda-senpai.
いや～助かりましたよ　邦枝先輩。
I'd thought you'd already gone home.
てっきり　先に帰ったもんだと
ばっかり…。
べっ　別に！
I-It's just that I was doing some work
as the class representative, that's all!
学級委員の仕事を任されたんで
おそくなっただけよ！
一緒に帰ろうとか　そんなこと
思ってないから！
I wasn't thinking about going
home together or anything!
Well, anyway... Feeding time for Baby Beel.
ま～とにかくベル坊のメシだな。
アイ！
Hey, at least thank her.
（古市）おい　お礼くらい言えよ。
あ～ワリ　助かったわ。
Sure... Sorry, thanks for that.
（邦枝）
いいのっ！お礼してもらうために
助けたんじゃないし！
It's fine! I didn't help
because I wanted your thanks!
He's really cool!
あの人　カッコよかったね～。
電気バリバリ！なんちて～！
All shocking and stuff!
Please wait!
（山村）待って下さい！
男鹿さん　お願いです！
どうか　このオレを→
Oga-san, please listen!
Please accept me as your
sworn little brother!
弟分にして下さい！
お願いします！！
Please!
（邦枝・古市・男鹿）あ？
（梓）あ？
は？
アイ？
It's started right after we transferred...
What'll you do? Those guys from Teimo
are totally gonna come for revenge.
In that case we'll just beat 'em up again.
That's no different than
when we were at Ishiyama!
I thought that with a new
school could finally come
a chance for a real change, to a pleasant
school life full of bittersweetness...
Furuichi-dono, if you want pleasant
bittersweetness, leave that to me!
Stay back, you oppressing, salty old man!
On the next Beelzebub:
May I Call You Brother?
You may call me as often as you wish!
Old fart.
What?!